NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING THE
FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
-Selamun aleykum.
- Alaikum salam, my brother.
You may have a seat.
If you’ll excuse me, I have things to do.
I wanted to talk about Nikola.
I’m listening, brother.
He isn’t the one behind the trap set for
me.
I wanted you to know.
You talk as if you don’t know about the
munition incident.
They were going to destroy everything.
I'm sure he is the one who bribed Yavlak
Arslan’s helper and set the trap.
I didn't say Nikola is innocent.
But I think Yavlak Arslan's helper and
Kuzgun gets support from elsewhere.
Why are you telling me this?
You are the First Alp.
I thought you would take precautions.
Are you trying to lecture me, Osman?
Not at all. (Istighfurullah)
Osman...
Listen to me carefully.
You are a Valiant…
... and brave…
… however…
... not everything you have on your
mind is true.
There were lots of conflicts at the Tent
last year.
I heard that you couldn’t cooperate
with our uncle and Gunduz brother.
Because of you, they got deceived by
our enemies.
What does ‘true’ really mean, brother?
Now that we are at the Tent…
... you can’t make us get deceived by
our enemies...
... just like you did last year.
If it weren’t for me...
... we wouldn’t be making this
conversation at this Tent, brother.
What happens in the past, stays in
the past.
From now on, everyone must know
their place.
When I say stop, you will stop.
When I say walk, you will walk.
And who decides that, brother?
My father, Ertuğrul.
And I, as your big brother.
I see that you got used to our father’s
chair.
And the coat suits you very well.
Very well.
Don’t…
... don’t you accuse me ever again.
I’m not here for the coat.
The things I hear and see are enough
for me.
Who doesn't love the chair and coat?
Those who sat on the chair with ambition…
... left it with disappointments.
Good luck with that.
Remove your hand, brother.
Take your words back.
Remove your hand, brother!
Did I stutter, Osman?
I said remove your hand!
Don’t you ever hit me again!
Know your place!
Take your words back!
I said nothing wrong!
TWO DAYS AGO
What happened here?
Mönke…
What about him?
How on earth, you couln’t handle a
single soldier, Kuzgun!?
You had lots of men with you.
The best soldiers in your service!
Osman…
… he is the devil himself, my Bey.
Devil himself, huh?
You are useless!
What will say to my father, Arslan?
Osman is going to give us everything we
want!
How?
Mönke…
What about him?
Speak!
My Bey!
Come here! It’s important.
Kuzgun.
Be cautious.
It seems they made him pay off.
And it seems they have a
message for you, my Bey.
He who sent this message has left
his mark too.
Let’s see.
It's a trap!
Osman.
Is he dead?
Let’s say his life worths more than his
flesh.
What about Kuzgun?
He is dead as it was necessary.
But his death is going to give us more
Osman's.
You have one last job.
What’s that?
You will go to Konya, to Geyhatu’s
presence.
He will make me worse than deceased.
Don’t worry.
He will treat you with respect.
You will tell Geyhatu about the
fate of his son.
What happened to Mönke?
Osman killed his Nükels and captured him.
He may have killed him by now and fed the
wolves with his corpse.
While you are on your way to Konya, I will
pay a visit to that old wolf.
My Bey, are you okay?
Are you okay, my Bey?
I'm okay.
Any sign?
We've looked everywhere sir but we
couldn’t find anything by now.
As if they are under earth.
They have removed the arrows from the
corpses.
It means they didn’t want to leave any
sign.
The Turks!
Only the Turks have these kind of bows
which can penetrate the bodies this deep.
How did they learn about it?
There is a spy in Castle Inegol.
Once again you did what you do
the best, Ali Chef.
It smells delicious.
My dear father.
Eleftheria, hurry up!
Tekfur Nikola is waiting for his supper.
The new Tekfur is very cautious and
he adores himself.
We must not draw attention.
Mighty Caesar, I’ve been working very hard
ever since I took the office.
And eventually, I’ve made my abawed
people believe in me.
These people, whose ancestors had found
the Roman Empire, became miserable!
Because of their useless leaders!
I’m going to establish a new army.
An army that will take us to the gates
of Jerusalem once again!
So this what the Mongols and Chinese
call flying fire.
I wish we could defeat every scourge
with this.
Be careful, uncle. Nikola probably knows
about the fate of his ammunition by now.
He will do everything to take it back.
Don't worry. I will take every necessary
precaution.
Tell them to be careful and not to get
close it with fire.
Thank you, my nephew.
You saved us all from a big trouble.
Thank you.
If Nikola had this munition…
Nikola…
Caesar is awaiting for your
greetings, Flaetus.
Mighty Caesar.
My old friend, is the flying fire in
my castle?
The Turks…
... they've found the munition and took
it away.
Ertuğrul…
A strong and intelligent enemy makes us
stronger in the end.
Where did they take it?
To Söğüt.
Then it means, the sun will rise at
midnight for Söğüt.
The lights of Heaven will surround
everywhere.
What about the plague I planted into
their seeds?
It kills everyone as we speak and knows
no faith.
I fear it’s the Plague, my Bey.
Plague?
What are you talking about?
It’s killing Söğüt day by day.
As if we don't have enough enemies.
My Rab, may you help us.
We must not get used to losing, Flaetus.
We can’t disappoint our people while they
expect hope from us.
I will take such revenge from the
Turks that...
... they will never dare to take anything
from us.
Do it without leaving any trace.
Don’t let the game of peace we play with
Ertugrul get understood.
For now.
Don’t worry.
You are making yourself sad by thinking
of that imbecile Dündar.
Never in my life, I smiled wholeheartedly.
At least, I can serve my Tent and my
brother.
This sacrifice of yours is going to soothe
us all.
Inshallah.
If one day we make Kayi Tent do what
we say, thanks to you…
... we will become stronger than ever.
Don’t have any doubts, my brother.
Ertugrul is lying on his deathbed.
Because of this, we can’t let go of
Kayi Tent.
I’m ready to do anything.
The power of Kayi has to be ours.
Nobody else’s.
Ertugrul Bey has just invited you to
his presence, Hazal Hatun.
Let's see Valiants.
Who’s going to win?
My Ahmet, throw it with the force of
your arm.
Mashallah.
My dear lions. Go on, continue!
Am I allowed, my Bey?
You may come in.
Little Alps.
Such intelligent children they are.
Just like everybody else who was born
and raised in the Tent of my Ertugrul Bey.
Not at all. (Istighfurullah)
They must learn everything by heart
especially at this age…
... so that they won’t get deceived very
easily when the time comes.
Are you mad at me?
Let’s say I’m rather disappointed.
Perhaps you are disappointed because
of your husband.
He left you and went to Sögut.
Since he left me and went somewhere
many times in the past…
... his infidelity doesn’t hurt me any
longer.
Hooray!
Mashallah!
Ahmet is the winner!
Ever since the Mongols arrived, the coins
are less valuable.
With the help of Allah (Inshallah), you
will able to issue your own coins.
With the help of Allah (Inshallah).
Now, you should train outside.
Hazal Hatun, you better understand that
Ertugrul Bey knows no family…
... when it comes to survival of the Tent.
Our people should also understand this
for the sake of our Law.
Then it means I’m the victim here.
Just like prophet Ishmael became the
victim.
You are free to go.
Thank you.
However...
... the path of your brother is no good.
He either opens his gates to the wrong
people...
... or he is controlled by his ambitions.
You know I like you.
Keep an eye on your brother.
As his sister, you should warn him.
Who am I to warn my brother, my Bey?
But I’d like to know if he has any flaws.
If he says no to his ambitions, everything
will be solved.
Thank you brother.
You endure the pain well, my Bey.
Have some bone broth brother.
It will make you feel better.
I’ve become a burden to you.
These enemies are clever.
They have something to do with
my father’s arrival at the Tent.
What do you mean, my Bey?
Their aim was to kill me.
They want to destroy our Tent.
Selamun aleykum, Alps!
Alaikum selam.
May your night be good.
Welcome, Kumral Abdal.
Please join us.
You’ve already made our night better.
Brother…
... he is a friend of the heart.
I will tell you later.
Welcome.
You worry way too much, Bey’s son.
Some secrets can’t be resolved.
It’s not always easy.
I don’t care about the number of our
enemies.
It’s natural for Valiants to have many
However, they wanted to separate me
from my father.
And they knew my father would be at
the Tent.
There is a thin line between knowing and
not knowing.
Solomon knew the language of birds.
He ruled many lands.
Everyone obeyed him.
What happened in the end?
He went to Heaven just like every mortal.
Teshubah!
He who may never die, Bey's son.
Let me tell you what happened.
Solomon who ruled animals, jinns,
people, and who shook the mountains
... once came across to an army of ants
while he was on expedition.
The ants said: “Scatter around! Solomon’s
army is going to crush us all!”
Solomon heard their screams.
Once again the ants said: “Please don’t
crush us and our brothers.”
Who is Solomon not to hear them
scream?
Who is he not to care about the right of
ants?
In the end, that mighty Solomon…
... Valiant Solomon…
... Solomon who cared about the
right of ants...
... ordered his men to change their route.
He cared about even the rights of
simple ants.
This is what true power means: always
caring about one’s rights.
May you be strong.
Please Alps.
Please.
Don’t you ever forget where the power
comes from and why it comes.
Always be conscious enough to hear
the voice of ants.
Amin.
He who may never die.
The voice of ants and warblers.
The voice of streams.
The voice of horses.
All is nothing but the miracles of our
creator.
He who hurts a life, hurts the creator.
May Allah bless your heart, Kumral Abdal.
It was a silent and peaceful night just
like this one.
The stars surrounded my father and I with
compassion.
The last night I saw my father.
The night, Ertugrul and his Alps sneaked
into Karacahisar Castle.
Sly as a snake, silent as a mouse.
It’s time to revenge that night.
You can no longer take
what’s ours, Ertugrul Bey.
No longer.
May your Ertugrul Bey protect you
from the power of flying fire.
There is going to be chaos in Söğüt
tonight.
Change your uniforms!
Be sneaky and spill it clever to
make your way out of Söğüt.
Fire it and run away.
You are all going to be heroes tonight.
They’ve stored the munition in
the depot, Flaetus.
You’ll revenge your sibling at Heaven.
I don't want to leave it to Heaven.
All I want to do is to be free from the
Turks so that I can open my tavern again.
Soon.
I’ll be your first customer.
This is the twentieth funeral
in Söğüt, my Bey.
Hazal.
My rose and companion.
Hatuns.
They prepared vinegars.
I brought them.
I know that your are mad and dissapointed.
You are sad because I didn’t stop my
brother and left you alone there.
It’s in your nature, Dündar Bey.
In your nature.
However, I know that you are innocent.
If I told you to stop, they would
have thought I was an imposter.
Who was trying to deceive Osman and
I didn’t want to add fuel to flames.
What’s happening?
There is no need to talk.
How’s the situation in Söğut?
Not good.
I closed all the entrances.
I know. I hardly convinced the Alps.
How are you going to feed all these
people?
Alps are carrying food and water to
families.
Hatuns of the Tent should work more
for hours.
It seems things are worse than we think.
Now that you are here…
I will get rid of this plague easily now.
Inshallah. Inshallah.
But, things will get
complicated in the Tent, Dündar Bey.
Keep your eyes open.
Why is that?
I saw the desire of power
in the eyes of Lena and Bala.
They are both ambitious.
They would both give
their lives for their Bey.
And you? Wouldn't you?
Die, you dogs!
Die!
What? What is happening?
Hazal, are you alright?
What is happening?
My Bey!
There were explosions,
we have many casualties!
What are you talking about?
Hazal.
Die!
Rest in peace, father.
Your son, Vladius,
has returned for revenge.
What is it, brother?
I hope it's for the good, brother.
I hope it's for the good.
I saw Söğüt in my dream.
It was blood everywhere.
It was burning.
Cowards attacked while my people
were dealing with the plague.
Those are the ones who
caused this plague, uncle.
You are very smart,
my nephew. Very smart.
- Am I allowed, my Bey?
- What is it, Saltuk?
A man says "It came."
Come on, don't keep me busy for nonsense!
Stop, uncle. It's important.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come.
We have... so many casualties, my Bey.
Tell Dündar Bey...
... to take care of the
ones who got hurt...
... to rebuild everywhere that's
been damaged, destroyed...
... and pay for every
expense of the ones...
... who have lost their parents,
both the Muslims, and non-Muslims.
By your orders, my Bey.
That Vladius coward did it.
Names of Vladius' men.
With these drawings, I will prepare such
a celebration for them in the castle...
Nephew, what would
my brother say for this?
We have ashamed my father, uncle!
I can not see my father
without ending this!
May seeing my father be forbidden to
me until I take our revenge for this!
He hasn't been around for a
long time, I hope it's not bad news.
Welcome, my Bey. I hope you liked
the goods you bought last time.
Thank you, you should
prepare a chestful of more.
By your command, my Bey.
Can I come in?
Come.
-Salaimun Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
You're late son. We were waiting for you.
Where were you, what were you doing?
Ertuğrul Bey. You came
to me and asked questions.
Now, I came to you and you ask again.
If this is special for me, I am flattered.
But, if you treat everyone
like this, I would be sad.
Because I would say " We weren't special
in the eyes of Ertuğrul Bey after all."
Are you hungry?
Should we set a table for you?
I came to see my sister Hazal.
And I decided to take her with me.
Her husband is Dündar.
Without his permission,
you can't even take her clothes!
No problem. Then we'll spill blood.
Bay Sungur, bring a chicken,
Yavlak Arslan will spill blood.
You can only cut a chicken in our Tent!
Osman Bey is coming!
May I die for your Allah! Look at you!
Thank Allah for this reunion!
What happened? Who set this trap?
Did you take lives?
Calm down, master Davut,
we will tell everything.
Yavlak Arslan is the guest of our Bey.
Your father was a Ghazi. A good one.
Because he wouldn't turn
to the Turkmen Tents...
... he would attack the enemy.
In which house you grew in, that you are
talking about spilling brothers' blood?
We would die for our
brothers if necessary.
But only if they look after their
entrusted, if they don't hurt them.
Osman Bey is here, my Bey.
Be Hazal's guest for a while,
I will fulfill my longing for my son.
Then we'll talk.
My Bey, thank Allah
for your safe return.
My Bala.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I will see my father.
Salaimun Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam, Arslan Bey.
I am sorry to hear about it, Osman.
A dog in our doors ashamed us all.
We have time to talk
about these, Arslan Bey.
Father.
I would die for you, my father.
You came.
I saw you.
Thank Allah.
I pass through many flames in your way.
I pass, but I am not hurt.
For I come to you, father.
I know, son. I know.
If you hadn't come,
our summer would be winter.
If something had happened to you...
My rage would be like
thunderstorms in all the world.
Know that.
I know, father. I know.
With Allah's permission, we will make
many tyrants bow under this banner.
I know that too.
Thank Allah for this reunion.
Ertuğrul Bey gave people a lesson with me.
He is a Bey. He gives
lessons, he cuts heads.
But he can't do that to us, sister!
I forgave his imbecile
brother and came here.
Look what they've done,
instead of being thankful.
Brother.
You set the trap on Osman, right?
My smart sister.
Let's call that,
reminding him his place.
Scratching his fame.
No one could surpass me in Turkmen lands.
That's certain. But...
... if they find out you did this-
Hazal, if I am stupid enough
to fall into my own trap...
... may the milk of my mother be haram,
may the sword of my father find me!
What is my place in this, brother?
They won't give up on this, sister.
Keep your eyes open, every
information is precious to me.
Sister, walk on snow,
but hide your tracks.
They wanted to kill me. Kuzgun
took refuge in Mongols.
They set a trap inside of a trap.
That is devil's nature!
Who could've done this, my Bey?
Yavlak Arslan could be in this.
We will watch, we will see.
When the time comes, we will understand.
Can I come in?
Come.
-Salaimun Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
Alaikum Salam.
Come, Arslan Bey.
My Osman, I am sorry for you, again.
Thank you.
I came, for it troubles me. They want
us to fight within ourselves.
Would the devil's game ever end?
It will continue until the end.
Kuzgun... Have you seen
anything about that Kuzgun dog?
I sent all my soldiers after that dog.
He was in Mongolian headquarters.
But...
Someone removed the tracks.
Of course they did, Osman.
The ones who set the trap,
can also remove the tracks.
But, haven't you seen anything?
Beys. Neither the devil...
... nor the good ones will stop.
Arslan, you came, you said you don't know
about it. We believe you. Thank you.
Not only Osman, if anyone from your
Tent gets hurt, my heart would burn.
Thank you.
My road is long.
If you'll excuse me.
Osman!
My Bala!
You were gone, I was no more.
I came, I've found life.
My heart bled, my tongue went silent.
I got hurt, you were my hope.
What is it?
Bring a pot. Bring a pot.
No water, brother Dumrul.
Yet you are still dirty.
You talk more than you help.
Brother Boran?
Here we go...
I have some business, brothers,
I should get going.
Brother, do everything,
but don't do this to us.
We would notice.
What? What did you notice?
Don't think us for idiots.
What would you say, if Osman Bey sees you
like this and says "Is there a wedding?"
Even the chickens in the Tent would
understand your intentions from your look.
What did my Bamsı Bey say? Leave no trace.
Thank you, you are right, brothers.
Thank you, brothers.
Your brother, Savcı has returned too.
Really, my Bala?
We even forgot our brother in all this.
It has been many years.
I haven't seen him in a long time.
My father sent him to Crimea last time.
Lena helped us very much.
Of course she did.
Thank Allah, our family
is being whole again.
By the way...
... your Alp, Boran,
is in love with Gonca.
Then tell your companion to not
be so hard on my Boran like you did.
We are Âhi women. Is that so easy to
conquer our hearts, Osman Bey?
I have experience because of you.
I will tell Boran to take caution.
I already trained Gonca for this.
Salaimun Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
Was it you?
Thank you.
She is stubborn, she won't give her milk.
If you don't know how to take it...
Is that so?
Come, then, take it yourself.
I won't, it's a woman's job.
Then, don't talk like you know about it.
If I take it, would you
race horses with me?
You won't be able to anyway.
Come.
Don't fail me, please.
Come on, Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Hey Mashallah!
Thank you.
We will race in Yeşilpınar,
you should come.
Brother!
Brother?
-Mashallah!
-My lion!
It's been a long while.
Thank Allah for this reunion.
Thank Allah, indeed.
Who was behind the ambush?
We couldn't find a mark, brother.
Did you come without a track from the hunt?
This is a hunt, brother.
We were unlucky.
I will reveal the one who ambushed
you and the ones who move against us.
Inshallah, brother. Inshallah.
Well, there was a raid at Söğüt?
Weasel Nicola tried to take revenge.
But I will give him the real hell.
I wonder what's on your mind, brother.
I want to help.
Get rest, my valiant. And don't abstract
yourself with these matters.
Your brother is here,
enjoy yourself.
What do you mean by enjoying, brother?
Aren't we here for each other?
You are wayworn, brother.
If I say don't worry, then don't worry.
Look here!
We are facing the enemy, the enemy!
What is this slackness?
What is this frailness?
Get up!
Attack!
If you fall, the army falls!
Get up!
One for all, all for one!
If you fall, you die!
If you die, we lose our army!
Come on, come on!
Welcome, my bey.
In an army...
...love is as important as fear.
-Do you know for what?
-For battle, my bey.
No.
For their commander.
They shouldn't fear their commander,
they should love him to death.
They should love so that they can run
to die when ordered to.
They aren't the Mongol army...
...and you aren't a Mongol warrior now.
Don't forget that.
Thank you, my bey.
May you live long.
For you, I will train an army that is ready
to die.
It will be such an army that...
...it will bring the Turk-Islam order
to the world.
Osman Bey.
I can take care of the rest.
Mind your business.
-These drinkers over there.
-Thank you, Zülfikar Dervish.
My Bey.
What makes you think?
I'm eating my heart out, Bala.
I'm eating my heart out.
The enemy is strong and so should we.
We need to strengthen the army.
If my brother Gündüz gets appointed
to Kuluca Hisar...
...and I get tasked by the
reformation of the army...
...then...
May I enter, Osman Bey.
I'm coming, my Bey.
What do you mean my Bey?
Of course, you can enter.
You are the Bey of where your
wife is.
Of course, I will ask.
Help yourself, father.
The dinner is ready, Ertuğrul Bey.
Thank you, my girl.
If you allow me.
With the name of Allah.
Tell me, Osman Bey.
What is the situation at the Tents?
Do the trees comply with their leaves?
The sheep with their lambs?
Brothers with brothers?
The trees are pleased with their fruits,
the sheep with their milk...
...and brothers with their brothers,
my bey. Thank Allah.
So, what's the situation of our Alps?
Our Alps are heroes. In a short time,
they became as capable as a swordmaster.
Our archers reached longest ranges of
the last five years. Our horses...
...are stronger than before, even faster.
-What is the situation of our equipment?
We have the arrows to pierce the
tyrants. The weapons to arm the innocent.
The sharpness of a weapon won't matter
to the plays of the enemy, son.
We will overcome with our minds,
destroy their games with our hands, father.
But...
Go on, but?
My Bey, what we lack is fire.
Our Alps need to warm up for
victories.
If you allow it...
...I want to be responsible for the
recovery of the army--
Every Alp will fight their own battle,
son.
After not being able to control their
conceit, wroth...
...even if they have the fire,
what they will burn is certain.
Victory belongs to ones who are
afraid to defy Allah's orders.
Three of you, prowl around.
You, come with me.
Enjoy it.
-Drink some of our holy water.
-Thank you, my monk.
This is our best day.
To our victory!
To reascension of the Byzantines!
Didn't I tell you to not drink that much?
Oh, Lena Hatun.
Let's finish this vinegar.
-Haven't anyone told you?
-Told me what?
That I'm an Orthodox Christian.
No.
This is why I loved Savcı Bey.
This is why I married him.
Who is who doesn't matter to him.
-How did you meet with brother Savcı?
-At Karacahisar.
Before Ertuğrul Bey conquered our castle.
My father was working for a wealthy noble.
He was a good navvy. He was working all day.
One day, when they were taking
the goods to the city...
...the cart topples down with
the goods.
The seigneur gets too mad and
he does cruelty to my father.
He tortures my father on the road,
without mercy.
He spills the blood of my father, who is
the most merciful man on this earth.
Until Savcı comes. He comes and saves
my father. Brings him home.
And becomes my hero.
As my father told me about his bravery,
I fell in love with him.
How did you make brother Savcı
fall in love with you?
With the name of Allah.
With the 99 names of Allah...
...who creates everything, who fills our
hearts with faith.
My beys.
-May Allah bless our council.
-Thank you.
Because of the plague in Söğüt...
...Dündar Bey assigned his authority
to Gündüz Bey.
It's appropriate.
As you ordered, my bey.
These are the decisions to take.
My beys.
This council is the council of
mind and heart.
We were one, we emigrated, we conquered
and we became a thousand.
We obtained castles, realms.
Meanwhile...
...our valiants took lives...
...and lost their lives.
But we saw that a strong
sword isn't enough...
...the mind should be at least as sharp.
Osman, my child...
...may you live long.
With both your sword and your mind,
you protected our Tents from Mongols.
You conquered important places.
But gaining victories don't matter,
preserving it does.
If we don't organize well...
...we will be ruined.
-Well said, my bey.
For this reason, I commend Kuluca Hisar
to my son, Gündüz.
I am happy and honored.
If I betray the fiduciary, may I sacrifice
my life for the sword of justice.
Thank you, my bey. Thank you, my bey.
-Thank you.
Dündar Bey is appointed to Söğüt.
He is afflicted with the plague.
No one from the Tents
will go there.
And the leader of our Alps will
be my son...
May I enter, my Bey?
Come, son.
Brother.
Where were you when these
men got murdered?
Answer me, soldier! Where were you
when these men got murdered?
How did they enter the castle, huh?
How did they enter the castle?
Answer me! How did they enter the castle?
Where was your sentry post, huh?
Answer me!
Get up!
My father died in Karacahisar Castle
because of bumblers like you!
I will kill you all!
Vladius!
Keep calm, my dear friend.
Keep calm.
They were my best men, Nicola.
They died because of these bumblers.
Your job isn't only protecting
this castle...
...these stone walls.
You protect our honor, dignity...
...reputation.
A simple mistake you will make...
...will ruin the future of our children.
-Are you the watch officer?
-Yes, sir.
-Didn't you hear anything?
-No, sir.
-Didn't you see anything?
I like caution.
You will see it.
You will hear it.
I will kill whoever did this, Nicola.
We will find them, Vladius.
We will find them.
We took our revenge, my Bey father.
An eye for an eye and a tooth for a tooth.
My beys..
...they will pay with a thousand for
a life they take.
My brother came from a campaign.
What campaign is this? Let us know
so we can share the happiness.
We killed Nicola's men who raided
us at Söğüt.
Except for Vladius.
Thank Allah.
May Allah bless your holy war, brother.
Thank you, brother.
Long live, Savcı Bey.
You rose onto us like the sun.
My beys.
First Alp of our Tents will be...
...my son, Savcı.
May Allah help us, my Bey.
Amin.
- I congratulate you, brother.
- Thank you, brother.
I want to hear about the Alps
after the council.
Of course.
Amin.
O' Allah, make our Tents, our people
victorious.
Don't leave us alone with our conceit,
with our desires.
- Amin.
- Al-fatihah.
Brother.
Brother, welcome.
Thank you.
- Brother.
Come with me, Savcı.
It would deeply sorrow me to...
..not be able to with him
while my brother..
...Argun Khan was sleeping.
But now, I see how painful his
death will be.
- This is nothing, sir.
- Go on, tell me!
Tell me more!
- Tell me!
- The poison...
...will tear his body as if he swallowed
thousand thorns.
Like this rebellious Turkish Bey,
his eyes bleed first...
...he will lose his skin,
his bones will be visible.
But he won't die.
Good.
My brother's death shouldn't be as
easy as this Turk's.
It should take months.
Maybe years.
Until I sway all the kurultai beys to
my cause...
...his death should be slow and painful.
Before Argun dies, I should see his
demon face.
I should mock the hatred on his eyes.
Then, my nephew's turn will come.
This won't be that easy, sir.
When the Khagan gets elected...
...I will buy all the Kurultai members,
one by one.
There is no door that can't be opened
with gold.
Mongol kurultai members, they
are all grasping.
It's very difficult to give
them enough gold, sir.
If the Seljuk treasury isn't enough...
...there are Turkish tribes...
...if that's not enough either,
the Christians.
I will gather the bribe money
to become tha khagan...
...from them.
But that means more taxes, sir.
Cerkutay begged to see you, Geyhatu.
Bring him.
İnegöl Castle
I'm sure that the Kayıs have a spy
in the castle.
First, they raided our ammunation...
...then they came and killed the soldiers
I raided Söğüt with.
Osman wasn't involved with either of them.
Who do you think Ertuğrul asigned
for this?
Gündüz?
Or Dündar?
Who?
Neither of them are capable.
Savcı.
Savcı, huh?
Why did you laugh?
Two sons of Ertuğrul who are candidate
of taking his throne.
Two pain in the neck.
Osman has no chance against Savcı.
Savcı is closer to the throne
in Ertuğrul's eyes.
You are wrong, Vladius.
Osman has something that Savcı don't have.
What is it?
You will find out. You will find out
when you find the spy.
Vladius, civilian or soldier...
...gain information about everyone
in the castle.
I know only one thing about the spy.
He was here long before Ertuğrul's sons.
- Who may that be?
- We'll find out.
I will train the soldiers personally.
I will taught them personally.
The war is on our doors.
The war is on our doors, Vladius.
Cerkutay, Balgay's dog.
So, you came here knowing that
you would die.
I came here to die honorably
by your hands.
Then...
- Die!
- For one last time, for one last time...
...allow me to serve you. Allow me to give
you an information more valuable than...
...my life.
More valuable than...
...your life, huh?
It's more valuable than your life
as well, Geyhatu.
More valuable than my life, huh?
What is it?
Your son, Möngke.
What happened to me son, speak!
Osman! He killed your warriors and
abducted Möngke.
I was wrong to look down on Osman.
I won't let my son pay the price with
his glory.
He won't kill Möngke.
How do you know?
He abducted Möngke because he is afraid
of your wroth. That's what I think.
My son isn't the matter...
...it's about my honor.
My honor!
Dead or alive,...
...my son can't give it back..
Only Osman...
If there is someone
who will give my honor back...
...It's Osman.
I will clean my honor with Osman's
and his family's blood.
Allow me to come with you.
My honor can only be cleaned...
...if I die for you.
Put on some clothes worthy
of a commander...
...who is under my command...
...then, come.
Osman Bey.
Ahmed Alp.
- Want to do a sword drill?
- Some other time.
- Want to wrestle?
I'll show you my muscles.
Tomorrow, Ahmed.
Are you coming from Ertuğrul Bey's tent?
Yes.
Osman Bey.
My father is dead.
Ahmed Alp.
Fathers never die, Ahmed.
Don't you ever forget that.
Like everlasting coal in the
hearts of their children...
...they are always alive.
Ahmed Alp.
Osman.
What happened to Osman Bey?
He seems mad.
I hope nothing is wrong.
I congratulate, Lena.
You came and made a scene.
What's wrong, Hazal Hatun?
Of course. Ertuğrul Bey...
...took the leadership of the Alps
from Osman...
...and gave it to Savcı Bey.
Savcı is working for his Tents.
I'm sure he deserved it.
What is a position's worth between
brothers, Hazal Hatun?
Be careful, women.
Look after your men.
We shouldn't bother with
brother fights at the Tents.
We just found peace.
Karayel, karayel...
Telling a strong stream to not flow...
Telling horses running on steppes
to stop...
Telling the winds to not blow,
is it suitable?
Isn't that a shame?
Tell me, Karayel. Tell me.
Would the wind stop blowing?
Would the horses stop?
Would the streams not flow?
Then, why do they tell me to stop?
Then, why do they tell me to
be silent?
Ah, Karayel, ah...
I tear my heart out.
My heart is boiling...
My Allah, give me patience.
Are you all right?
Come.
- Come, take a breath.
- I'm fine.
The nausea increased recently.
I believe I'm pregnant.
Mashallah.
- Does Savcı Bey know it?
- Not yet.
- He will be so happy.
- Wouldn't he. He always says that a man...
...need many children to make
a reputation.
- Lena.
- I'm coming, my bey.
Thank you.
Lena.
Tell me, what is it?
It's not that easy.
- Why is that?
- You waited that long.
I won't say it that easily.
Put some effort.
Look for cures if necessary.
It's rumored by the people...
...that Bala Hatun can't
have a baby.
One day, they can get into Osman's
head.
Men don't have much patience.
One day, you might be sharing
your tent with another woman.
- Will you tell me?
- I will.
Tell me then.
Come, sit. I'll tell you my secret.
It's not appropriate to sit there.
Why? Won't you sit there
when the time comes.
No one can know that. First, it's up to
Allah, then to my father and the beys.
You became the First Alp.
We both know what's next.
Still, you shouldn't say that.
You deserve the throne, in the eyes
of your father and the beys.
Only you, Savcı.
Only you.
Come, sit here.
Come on, we are alone.
Come on.
Now, close your eyes.
You may open them.
Lena?
Are you?
When I was pregnant
for Bayhoca, you gifted me this.
I never took it off and prayed every day
for a son.
I will be praying again.
We will have another child, Savcı.
Kayı Tents' future Bey will have another son.
Thank Allah.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam, brother.
Come.
I have things to do.
If you allow me.
I wanted to talk about Nicola, brother.
I'm listening, brother.
He isn't behind the trap set against me.
I wanted you to know.
You speak like you don't know the
ammunition incident, brother.
They were going to blow off everywhere.
He is the one who bought Yavlak Aslan's...
...helper and set the trap for you.
I'm not saying that Nicola's intentions
are pure.
But, there is someone else behind Yavlak
Aslan's helper, Kuzgun.
Why are you telling me this.
You are the First Alp.
I thought you could take measures.
Do you think I need your counsel, Osman?
Not at all, brother.
Osman, listen, brother
You are valiant.
You are a warrior.
But...
...everything you think isn't
true.
The Tents had been through a lot
last year.
You couldn't move together with my uncle,
with my brother Gündüz.
You went your way and they
were deceived by the enemy.
What is the truth, brother?
Now, we are at the Tents.
Neither you will go your own way.
Nor we will let the enemy
deceive us.
If it wasn't for my struggle last year...
...we wouldn't be talking at this
tent today, brother.
The past is past and the present is
present.
From now, everyone will know their places.
Everyone will move when they are told to
move and stop when they are told to stop.
- Who will decide on that, brother?
- My father, Ertuğrul.
And your older brother, I.
You got used to my father's position.
The fur fits you so well.
So well.
Never.
Never accuse me.
Our eyes aren't on the fur.
What I heard and saw is enough for me.
Both the fur and the position were
loved my many.
Those who sat with passion,
got up with disappointment.
Good luck with that.
- Take your hands off me, brother.
- Take it back.
Take off your hands, brother.
- Osman, I won't repeat myself.
- I told you to take off your hands, brother!
Never hit me again!
Know your place!
- Take it back!
- I didn't say anything to take back.
There will be blood, Davud brother.
Thank Allah, Ertuğrul Bey isn't here.
My lion brother! Mashallah to my valiant!
You are getting stronger every day!
My lion brother.
Long live!
Savcı Bey, mashallah.
You got even stronger.
My lion brother.
My dear brother...
My dear...
The fight for the fur has fired up.
Long live!
Geyhatu...
- It doesn't lack salt, does it?
- What's this haste, my hanım?
We are preparing dinner for Ertuğrul Bey.
Women should turn the tent into
heaven with their meals.
Bala Hatun went missing while
preparing dinner.
If she is missing, why do you care?
Is it your job? Mind your own work.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
- I left all the trouble for you.
- What trouble, Bala Hatun?
- It's our duty.
- You just came.
- You are working before resting.
- I carried this tent's burden for years.
Be at ease.
How is Osman Bey?
Did he calm down?
Osman Bey is in a good mood.
He will take care of the Tent's
affairs and rest for a while.
Last year, my valiant couldn't sleep
because of running one battle after another.
Thank Allah.
The dinner is ready, my Bey.
May Allah bless your hands, girls.
With the name of Allah.
Enjoy your meal.
What's up?
You stopped the spread of the plague
in Söğüt. Is this why you are happy?
We are receiving good news from
both Söğüt and İnegöl Castle.
My nephew, Savcı, hit a severe
blow to the castle.
The echo of his slap
is still there, they say.
Sounds of whippings didn't end
until morning in the castle.
Nicole went mad with anger.
First Alp, my valiant son, Savcı.
You gave Nicola a good lesson.
When Nicola plans cunningness...
...he will think more than twice now.
Thank Allah, our Tents are in good
hands now.
Ertuğrul Bey is leading us.
Our beys are...
...doing their jobs.
Now, everyone should work harder than
ever before.
Not only beys or Alps...
...women too.
As you order, my bey.
- As you order, my bey.
What's wrong, my Bey father?
What is it that you know and we don't?
I heard that Geyhatu is on his
way with his army.
They say that he is coming to
raze Söğüt to ground...
...exterminate the Kayıs.
In a few days, the songs of
the birds won't be heard...
...because of the horses of
their warriors.
We know how to stop Geyhatu as we
stopped Balgay and Subutay before.
It's time to keep valiantness on its
sheath...
...until the right time comes, Osman.
Hence...
...we need to send a messenger
to Gethatu...
...whose tongue is as sharp as
his blade.
If you allow me, I apply for the mission.
I know that all the beys here...
...would do this mission without fear.
But I will give this mission
to Savcı.
Before sunrise, go swiftly, Savcı.
As you order, my bey.